Faruk Burak Öğretici

Jr.Full Stack Developer

Istanbul, Turkey ☐ fburakogretici@gmail.com 1+90-5437668508



Hello, I'm Burak, I've always had an interest and enthusiasm for software, and I've worked in various companies as a software developer for the last two years. I continue to improve myself every day. I am a curious and ambitious person who likes to research. While writing code, I pay attention to SOLID principles and writing clean code.

EXPERIENCE

05.2022- 02.2023 Full Stack Developer(ASP.NET MVC)

Omicron Bilişim

11.2021-05.2022 Full Stack Developer(ASP.NET MVC)

DataSurgery(intern)

01.2022-04.2022 Full Stack Developer(ASP.NET)

Fenomio(contractual)

EDUCATION

09.2019-06.2023 Faculty of Applied Sciences – Management Information Systems

Bandırma 17 Eylül University

09.2015-06.2019 Mehmet Pisak Anatolian High School

SKILLS / COMPETENCIES

Language	Abilities/Competencies	Tools & Techn	Tools & Technologies	
English -> B2	Programming	C# -> 3	PostgreSQL -> 2	
Turkish -> Mother tongue	Leadership	.Net MVC -> 3	$MSSQL \rightarrow 3$	
	Algorithm	JavaScript -> 2	Angular -> 2	
	Business Analytics	Jquery -> 2	React -> 1	
		MS Office -> 3	Java -> 2	

SEMINARS & CERTIFICATES

2021 C# 2020 JavaScript 2020 MSSQL

Btk Akademi/Online Udemy/Online Udemy/Online

PROJECTS

2020 Rent a Car/Backend:

https://github.com/burakogretici/ReCap-Backend-Project

Rent a Car/Frontend:

https://github.com/burakogretici/ReCap-Frontend-Project

2022 E-Commerce:

https://github.com/burakogretici/ECommerceProject

HOBBIES

- Programing
- Take a walk
- Camping
- Watching movie

REFERANCES

Omicron Bilişim 0532-341-13-77

Behlül Behram – Managing Partner

Datasurgery 0533-247-13-15

Yeşim Köle – Team Leader

OTHER

Github: https://github.com/burakogretici

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/burakogretici/